<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
      <title>Atomic Reference on Atomic Reference </title>
      <generator uri="https://gohugo.io">Hugo</generator>
    <link>https://vrcca.github.io/</link>
    <language>en-us</language>
    
    
    <updated>Tue, 05 Mar 2019 16:47:29 UTC</updated>
    
    <item>
      <title>About</title>
      <link>https://vrcca.github.io/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 05 Mar 2019 16:47:29 UTC</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://vrcca.github.io/about/</guid>
      <description>Hi! I am a software developer writing about software development stuff. This is basically my knowledge dump, however I hope it helps you as well.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Contact</title>
      <link>https://vrcca.github.io/contact/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 05 Mar 2019 16:46:58 UTC</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://vrcca.github.io/contact/</guid>
      <description>   </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Getting The Current Page in Phoenix Framework</title>
      <link>https://vrcca.github.io/post/getting-the-current-page-in-phoenix/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 05 Mar 2019 16:31:19 UTC</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://vrcca.github.io/post/getting-the-current-page-in-phoenix/</guid>
      <description>When programming in Phoenix Framework, you sometimes need to code a decision point based on the current page. To do this, we can make use of Plug.Conn&amp;rsquo;s path_info field and compare it with Routes.
Let&amp;rsquo;s say you have the following piece of code:
&amp;lt;%= if is_accounts_page(@conn) %&amp;gt; &amp;lt;div&amp;gt; # Account related content &amp;lt;/div&amp;gt; &amp;lt;% end %&amp;gt;  To find out if the user is in the account route, you can compare the current path with the Account page route in LayoutView:</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Writing Better Tests In Java</title>
      <link>https://vrcca.github.io/post/writing-better-tests-in-java/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 30 Oct 2018 12:14:02 UTC</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://vrcca.github.io/post/writing-better-tests-in-java/</guid>
      <description>Ever wondered why your tests break everytime you change production code? Are your tests difficult to read? This usually happens due to tests being too attached to the corresponding implementation. I will show a few techniques on how to writte better tests in Java.
PS.: I will call &amp;laquo;Production Code&amp;raquo;, the code that you write to make your tests pass.
Changing Production Code Breaks Many Tests When your tests are too specific and bound to its implementation, you will notice that any changes to the production code such as extracting a method, extracting a class, and others, breaks your unit tests.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Hello World!</title>
      <link>https://vrcca.github.io/post/my-first-post/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 18 Oct 2018 15:21:02 UTC</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://vrcca.github.io/post/my-first-post/</guid>
      <description>Hello world! Here is my first post.
I shall begin it explaining how I setup this blog using GitHub Pages, GitLab and Hugo.
Creating a new GitHub Pages To setup a new GitHub page, the website tutorial is pretty straightforward, so I will skip this.
Hugo Hugo is a static website generator built on Go. It is extremely fast and requires little setup to start using it.
To install it is as simple as:</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Search</title>
      <link>https://vrcca.github.io/search/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 09 Nov 2014 13:49:44 &#43;0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://vrcca.github.io/search/</guid>
      <description>      $(document).ready(function() { $(&#39;#tipue_search_input&#39;).tipuesearch({ &#39;mode&#39; : &#39;json&#39;, &#39;show&#39;: 10, &#39;newWindow&#39;: true, &#39;wholeWords&#39;: false }); });     </description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>

